搞什么? 条子就停在对街
Fuck is he doing? Cops still parked right up the block.
怎么 我们隐身了?
What are we, invisible?
傻逼黑小子
Stupid fucking yos.
不是 就想整整他
Nah, just fucking with him, man.
要等他卖给谁吗
You want to wait for him to serve somebody?
才怪 他们已经犯法了
Fuck it.They're dirty either way
手扶墙 混球们
Hands on the wall, fuckers.
- 我们什么也没干! - 真的
- We ain't done nothing! - Seriously.
我不过是坐在椅子上看杂志
I was just sitting in my chair reading a magazine.
你是说边看着你的人藏毒?
Watching your crew work a ground stash, you mean?
我操
What the fuck?
混蛋!
Asshole!
你们都要付出代价
Y'all taking a charge for this, you know that?
- 你旷课 - 今天周六
- You're a truant. - Today's Saturday.
你周三试试
Try Wednesday.
我不用上课了 你们抓我干嘛
I'm past truancy, why y'all locking me up?
Colicio
Hey, Colicio.
是Colicchio警官 傻逼
Officer Colicchio, shitbird.
有必要这条路堵得死死的吗
We need to block every lane here?
别按了 警察执法
Shut it down. It's a police operation here.
- 把车倒一下 - 不好意思 警官
- Let's back these vehicles up. - Excuse me, officer.
- 别让我再说第二次 - Tony 冷静点
- I'm not telling you again. - Tony, calm down.
警官 如果你能把车稍微往前...
Officer, if you could just move your car forward just a little bit...
我们是警察!
We're the police!
你们干嘛 放开我
What are you doing? Let me go!
* When you walk through the garden *
火线重案组 第五季 第4集
The.Wire S05E04
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
www.1000fr.net presents
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
现在是买家市场   --Templeton
- 靠! - 有麻烦吗
- Fuck! - Problem?
我一整天都在追查Clay私人户头上的
I spent all day trying to trace this $80,000 withdrawal
一笔8万块的支取 我怀疑是脏钱
from Clay's personal account, figuring it was dirty.
结果他是还向岳母借的一笔款
Turns out he's repaying a loan from his mother-in-law.
- 借款? - 对 肯定是
- A loan? - Yeah. Has to be.
她2002年给了他相同数目
She gives him the same amount in 2002.
用以支付那周他买的一处房产的首期
He uses it as a down payment on a property that he buys the same week.
你看
See?
他六年前Calvert郡买了间度假屋
He bought a weekend house down in Calvert County six years ago.
贷款申请查了吗
You pulled the loan application on the property?
等等 给
Just a second. Here you go.
逮住他了
Got him.
- 一枪爆头 - 什么
- The head shot. - What?
如果有人暗示我破坏了指挥链
If anyone is suggesting that I've broken chain of command,
说我在你背后搞小动作
that I've gone behind your back,
说我想方设法拆你台 那纯属造谣
that I've lobbied against you in any way, they're lying.
我不知道是谁透露给报纸的 但他们是在撒谎
I don't know who told the newspaper that, but they were lying.??
嗯
Yeah.
长官 我不知道这事儿从何而来
Respectfully, sir, I don't know where this shit is coming from.
长官... 没人跟我说起过 Carcetti没有 其他人也没有
Sir...no one has spoken to me. Not Carcetti, not anyone.
但如果有人问我 我会拒绝这一职位
But if I'm approached, my answer will be to decline the position
表示我愿为您效劳
and say I serve at your pleasure.
长官?
Sir?
我该用Preakness赛马还是消防员之死?
Go with the Preakness piece or this one about the firefighter death?
- 你去面试哪家 - 弗吉尼亚分部的都市板块
- What are you interviewing for? - Metro position, Virginia bureau.
消防员好了 总得展示一下 我截稿日前写好的东西
Firefighter, I think. Got to show something I wrote on deadline.
- Burrell今天可能会被解雇 - 谁说的
- Burrell might get the ax today. - Who told you that?
东区的值班警官说整个警局都传开了
Desk sergeant in the eastern says it's all over the department.
- 祝我好运吧 - 祝好运
- Wish me luck. - Good luck.
有传言Burrell不是明天就是今天会被炒
Got a rumor that Burrell is gonna get fired today if not tomorrow.
是吗
Yeah?
- 你去跟吧 - Twigg呢
- Work it. - What about Twigg?
- 我是说 他消息来源不少 - 我总不能让他在职最后一天还干活吧
- I mean, with his sources? - I can't throw one at a guy on his last day.
你尽力跟吧
No, you work it as best you can.
现在你是我新的资深警讯记者了
You are now my new senior cop reporter.
无人认领 今年到目前为止... 11
Unclaimed. So far this year... 11.
如果算上我还没冷冻室里 我还没鉴定的两具就是13了
13 if we add the two in the freezer I ain't I.D.'d yet.
查查没有固定住址的
Run it for no fixed address.
Jimmy 如果我知道你在找什么更容易查
Jimmy, it'd help if I knew what the fuck you were looking for.
从尸体状况上看 我想知道在哪儿发现的死亡流浪汉最多?
Where are we pulling most of the homeless from?
有没有吸毒过量 芬太奴出现后死亡数大增
With or without ODs? Numbers are way up since Fentanyl showed up.
- 算进去吧 越多越好 - 好吧
- Throw 'em in. The more, the merrier. - All right.
靠!
Damn!
他们都死了 没有固定住址?
They're all dead and no fixed address?
像苍蝇一样横尸南部啊
Dropping like flies in the southern lately.
Lester 是我 对 在停尸房
Lester, it's me. Yeah, in the morgue.
有些在4点到12点 多数在午夜
Some 4 to 12, with a lot at midnight,
多数在南巴尔的摩
and a lot of them in South Baltimore.
对 南部12点到8点当班的是谁
Yeah. So who do we know working 12 to 8 in the southern?
分局警号2300 行啦
2300 at the district. That'll work.
Jimmy 我错过了什么吗
Jimmy, am I missing something here?
这对你有什么用
How does this help you?
我不要那种假装帮派分子的玩意
Don't want none of that phony gangster shit.
他很老派
He was old-school.
真有意思 我觉得我认识Butchie 但我就是认不出来
Funny, feel like I should know Butchie, but I can't place him.
白手起家
Came up under Teensy.
有次被人打了 眼睛瞎了
Caught him a slug early.  Took his sight.
偶尔搀上一脚 但始终谨小慎微
Dabbled now and then but kept it quiet as a puppy walking on cotton.
这个不错
This here do just fine.
写上"Butchie 祸哉 那些称恶为善 称善为恶的人" (圣经以赛亚书5:20)
Have it say, "Butchie. Woe to them that call evil good, and good evil."
签名"真挚而忠诚的友人Proposition Joe"
Sign it, "Your true and loyal friend, Proposition Joe."
你不会认为一条善意的挽联 就能让Omar不找我们麻烦吧
You ain't thinking no kindly note gonna slow Omar coming at us.
我是这么觉得的 他是个好人
It's how I feel. He was a good man.
- 那Marlo呢 - Marlo是Marlo 伙计
- And Marlo? - Marlo is Marlo, man.
害我到这步田地的又不是他
He weren't the one that put me in this trick bag.
是那个向Marlo告密的二五仔
The motherfucker who snuggled up and whispered in Marlo's ear did that.
我知道你在想什么 但我绝不会动自己亲人
I know what you thinking, and I ain't making a move against no kin,
除非言语无法解决问题
not till I got more to go on than words.
就我对我侄子的了解 如果那小子口袋里有五万大洋
And knowing my sister's son the way I do, if the boy got 50 grand in his pocket,
那笔钱很快就会跑进别人口袋里
it ain't gonna be long before it jump out and find itself in some salesman hand.
臭小子就那德性
And that kind of goody, we know.
同时 如果Omar找上门来 肯定会对付我
In the meantime, if Omar coming for any of us, he coming for me.
出于对他实力的尊重
And out of respect for that man's skill set,
明天会后 我会暂时退居二线
I'm gonna take myself out of the lineup after the meet tomorrow.
事情了结前 Cheese看店
Till this shit sort itself out, Cheese gonna watch the shop.
你看着Cheese
You gonna watch Cheese.
很干净 很好
Very clean. Very nice.
但没必要
But, this is unnecessary.
我们不想误导你
It was not our intent to mislead.
我之前说你钱的情况时
When I spoke before, about the condition of your money,
我是... 象征性的说法
I was talking... in symbols.
这钱来自街道
The money, it came from the street,
所以我认为你也来自街道
and so I thought you came... from the street.
我以前是 现在也是
I did. I do.
我关心的不是钱
It was not the money that concerned me.
你很大方
You have been more than generous,
显然这是一位可敬的绅士的礼物
and this is a gift of an honorable man, clearly.
但要是接受这份礼物 我们可能会给你一个错误的印象
But, in accepting such a gift, we would give you the wrong impression.
你来自街道?
You come from the street?
街道... 也不成问题
The street... doesn't concern us.
在这我们认识一个人 我们信任他
We know a man here,and we trust him.
但... 认识更多人 知道更多名字
But... to know more people, to learn more names,
让更多人知道我们...
to have them learn our names...
我不是来说Prop Joe坏话的 但我手下还指望我呢
I'm not here to badmouth Prop Joe but people depend on me.
去年我们遭劫了
Now, last year, there was a robbery.
我是说 要是再发生怎么办
I'm saying, you know, what if this happens again?
- 我手下怎么办 - 这个你跟Joe谈啊
- Where do that put my people? - That's for you to discuss with Joe.
我只想要一份保险
All I'm asking for is an insurance policy.
- 你知道的 能保护你我的 - 还有保护Joe
- You know,something covers me and covers you - And covers Joe.
小伙子说的有道理
The young man makes a point. You're right.
非常时期
These are volatile times
有个保险不是坏事
It is not unreasonable to carry insurance.
谁知道明天会怎样呢
Who can say what tomorrow will show us?
你去吧 小心点
You go. Be safe.
你的箱子
Your case.
你们大老远跑来 就当路费吧
Oh, y'all came a ways. Put it to expenses.
如果我们拒绝他 他还会再来
If we were to tell him no, he will still come back.
他表现得很明显
This he shows us.
但他不是Joe
But he is not Joe.
他的确不是Joe
He is not Joe.
看我理解了没 参议员岳母给了他8万
If I follow this, the senator's mother-in-law gave him $80,000
他用以支付某处房产的首期
that he used as a down payment on some property.
之后 他还了这笔钱 所以这是笔贷款
Later, he paid the money back, which makes it a loan.
这就构成了虚假贷款
Which falsifies the loan application.
他签署申请那刻就暴露了
The moment he signs the application, he's exposed.
联邦法典18编47章1014节
Title 18 of the U.S. Code, chapter 47, section 10-14,
贷款和信用申请
Loan And Credit Applications.
30年刑期 罚金不超过1百万
30 years and not to exceed $1 million.
联邦律师办公室称之为"一枪爆头"
The U.S. Attorney's office, call it "the head shot."
因为每个大学生买房会做的事判30年
30 years for something that every college kid does with a starter home.
老爸借钱让你具备购房资格
Daddy loans you money to qualify;
几年后 再把钱还上 30年
a couple years later, you pay him back. 30 years.
像这种举债经营 案子得告上联邦
With leverage like that, this case needs to go federal.
干得漂亮 警探 给我些时间消化
Outstanding work, Detective. Let me have some time to digest this.
律师 聊两句?
Counselor, a moment?
还有别的方法吗 偷窃罪证据充分吗
Is there another way to go at this? How strong are our theft counts?
有典型案例 四条罪状
Straightforward document cases, four counts.
他窃取自己的善款
He stole from his own charities.
定他的罪 每条罪判10年
We convict, that's ten years per count.
即便不算上银行债务也够他受的了
Nothing to sneeze at, even without the bank charge.
你觉得让我参加你们的预算会议合适吗
You think it might be OK for me to sit in on one of your budget meetings?
情况好的时候没问题
On our good days.
Ed? 这位是Scott Templeton
Ed? This is Scott Templeton.
Scott 很高兴见到你 请坐
Scott, good to meet you. Have a seat.
稍等
Give me a sec.
下个月要帮的是右派牧师Isaac Cason
Next mouth needs fed is the Right Reverend Isaac Cason.
老天! 搞得我像逼Ray Lewis退役似的 (巴尔的摩乌鸦队中后卫)
Christ! ???
我不过想踢掉Burrell
All's I'm trying to do is dump Burrell.
你想让我们接受Rawls 最好满足我们的要求
You want us to swallow Rawls, you'd better grease that morsel up good.
Rawls顶6个月 然后Daniels上位
Rawls for 6 months, then Daniels.
怎么 Daniels在你们眼里还不够黑吗
What, Daniels isn't black enough for you guys?
他们不认识他
They don't know him.
他们认识Burrell 有需要时可以求助于他
They know Burrell, and they could phone when they needed.
Burrell拿着一堆破统计数据 当着我的面撒谎
Burrell came in here with bad stats. He lied to my face.
Rawls也撒谎 但你却任命他代理局长
Rawls lied, too, but you're making him acting commissioner.
不过是等Daniels上位 我们不能一次炒掉所有人
Only till Daniels gets groomed. We can't fire everyone all at once.
- 这样吵下去没个结果  - Tommy 就剩两个了
- This isn't getting us anywhere. - Only two more left.
好吧 我怎么才能帮到这位可敬的Cason
Fine. How can I be of assistance to the good Reverend Cason?
他有处房产想转成老年住房
He has property he wants to convert to senior housing.
我们能给他调一下吗
Can we accommodate him?
我们没钱了 但可以给他弄点 住房及城市发展部的钱
We're broke, but we could steer some Hud money his way.
那就剩Myrtle Smith教士了
That leaves Reverend Myrtle Smith.
她想把她教堂边的空地拓展成停车位
She wants to extend parking to a vacant lot next to her church.
- 那是市里的地产 - 就这样了?
- It's city property. - That's it?
- 最后的也是最无关紧要的 - 一份长期租约 象征性付点钱
- The last is the least. - A long-term lease, dollar a year.
那就剩Mcculloh住房了
Then there's the matter of Mcculloh Homes.
那个Mcculloh住房紧邻州办公室
The same Mcculloh Homes that's adjacent to Andy Krawczyk's $300 million expansion
- Andy Krawczyk300万的开发区 - 超过500个单元
- of the state office complex. - Over 500 units.
公共住房 那需要"希望六"的钱 (美国公共住房项目)
Public housing. You'll need that Hope VI money for that.
- 希望六有钱吗? - 那无关紧要 先生们
- Is there any Hope VI money? - It doesn't matter. gentleman
议长女士只是希望我们开绿灯
All madam president wants from us is the green light.
你想让他走人 不是吗
You want him gone, right?
很好啊 你的一些栏目语言方面
It's good stuff.  Some of your feature  work is a little wrought
跟我们比起来有点精致 但原创性很明显
for what we do here language-wise, but it all shows initiative.
他们要的就是我这种风格
That's the style they want from me
但说实话 我宁可写得幽默点
but to tell you the truth, I prefer to write it dry.
- 你在巴尔的摩待很久了吗 - 两年了
- You've been in Baltimore long? - Two years.
在此之前 我在堪萨斯星报待了三年
Before that, I was at the Kansas City Star for three years,
那之前是威奇托鹰报
Wichita Eagle before that.
太阳报不错啊
The Sun's a fine paper.
裁员前是不错
Before the cutbacks, maybe.
他们在安纳波利斯还是能经常击败我们
Well, they still beat us often enough in Annapolis
我马里兰的编辑部都很在意他们
for my Maryland desk to take them seriously.
你有参与去年地租那件事的报道吗
You have anything to do with those ground rent stories last year?
那是好新闻啊 真心好新闻
It's good stuff, real good stuff.
你想去看看头版会议是吧
You wanted to go to the page one meeting, right?
下次吧
Another time, maybe.
总之 像他说的 我们会保存着你的简历
Anyway, as he says, we'll keep the resume on file.
再找些剪报和时效性文章 我们再谈 行吗
A few more clips, a little more seasoning, we'll take another look, OK?
那个可以扔了
You can just toss that.
计划是让他在副局长位置上积累些经验
That's the plan -let him cut his teeth as deputy for operations,
六个月内任命他
and in six months, make him.
他没他们想的那么清白
He's not the spic-and-span boy they think he is.
他出身东区一个坏缉毒队
He came up in the eastern district, part of a bad drug unit
他们私吞赃款
that was skimming seized drug money.
我有联邦官员...
I actually had the feds...
这跟Daniels无关 你伪造数据
This isn't about Daniels. You came in with bad stats.
在市长看来 那是最后一根稻草
For the mayor, that was the last straw.
我的数据没问题 都经过检查 你告诉Carcetti...
My numbers were clean, they had gone through staff review. You tell Carcetti...
Ervin 没用了
Ervin, it doesn't matter now.
你玩完了 Carcetti已经对你出手了
You're done. Carcetti has moved on you.
你告诉他如果那样对我 我就整Daniels
You tell him if he does me like this, I'll do Daniels.
如果你弄垮Daniels 结果就是Bill Rawls当局长
??Kill Daniels, and we end up with Bill Rawls as police commissioner.
部长 干部 议会 他们能容得下Daniels 为什么呢
The ministers, the caucus, the council - they'll live with Daniels. Why?
因为Carcetti为了让你滚蛋慷慨解囊
Because Carcetti gave away the store just to push you out.
每人30个银币是吧 (犹大出卖耶稣的价)
30 pieces of silver each, huh?
我们会罩着你的 我保证
We'll have your back. I promise you.
全额养老金和一个 市刑事司法协调理事会的职位
Full pension and a job on the mayor's criminal justice coordinating council,
还能在华盛顿谋一个
and from there, something down in Washington
警察协会的职位 保证能拿六位数
with one of the police associations - six figures guaranteed.
别走错路 会有人挺你 Ervin
Go the right way, and attention will be paid.
但你非要闹腾的话 没人...
But you go kicking and screaming, and no one -
干部们 部长们 包括我
not the caucus,not the ministers, not me -
都不会支持你
will be there for you.
你自己选吧
Your choice.
明天新闻发布会 你走完这过场吧
Press conference tomorrow. You play out the string.
Carcetti也会一样
Carcetti will do the same.
- 没人说点什么吗 - 我知道 我以为你能帮上忙
- No one's saying anything? - I thought you might be able to help.
- 非正式的也没有? - 他告诉过你
- Not even off the record?  - ???He told you.
二版的截止时限快到了 有什么消息了
E-dot deadline's creeping up. Where are we at?
法院有人说是真的 他在市政厅听说了
One source at the courthouse says it's true, he heard it at the hall.
市长办公室还没消息 明天有个新闻发布会
The mayor's office isn't saying anything, but there's a press conference tomorrow.
- 那总部那边呢 - Daniels不发表评论
- What about headquarters? - Daniels had no comment,
- Rawls不回我电话 - 靠 靠 靠
- and Rawls won't return my calls. - Fuck.
Templeton上哪去了 他也该在打电话才对
Where the hell is Templeton? He could be throwing calls, too.
我给你的最后一份礼物 Gus
My last gift to you, Gus.
Stan? 我是Twigg 我快要截稿了 别跟我来那套
Stan? It's Twigg, and I'm on a deadline, so cut the bullshit.
别告诉我他们要炒掉局长你不知情
Don't tell me they're firing the police commissioner and you don't know ??
别跟我说这个
Don't fucking tell me that.
幸亏我把你保出来 否则你就得去少管所了
Lucky I signed off on your ass, or you'd be on your way out to boys' village.
看你是怎么对我的
And look how you do me.
不来看我 不让我见Bug 你就这么回报你母亲的吗
Not coming around,not letting me see Bug. Is that how you pay back a mother?
- 我要怎么回报你 - 站住 放尊重点
- How should I pay you back? - Start by showing a little respect.
就这样?
That all?
事实上 我一直过得很困难
Truth is, things have been rough around the way
你赚了不少 我想你也许能给我些钱
With you doing so good, thought maybe you'd throw some ends my way.
你看我现在是怎么对你的
Seeing as how I was here for you.
我不会付钱让你当我妈
I ain't paying you to be my mother.
市局的行家光临了啊
The pros from downtown are here.
有什么能为两位效劳的
What can I do for you gents?
你有轮班名单吗
You got a copy of the shift roster?
- Oscar不是弄了个地产经纪执照吗 - 那是他白天的工作
- Didn't Oscar get a Realtor's license? - That would be his day job.
我青涩的巡逻期最爱的搭档啊 谢了
My favorite side partner from my salad days in patrol. Thank you.
真难想象你巡逻的样子
Hard to imagine you in patrol.
- 靠 找得到才怪 - 所以才叫坑啊
- Damn, if I can find it. - That's why they call it a hole.
这是最变态的想法 你知道吧
That there is the sickest idea yet. You know that?
我这是帮你出谋划策 小子
I'm just gilding your lily, son.
那儿 就那儿
There. Right there.
滚开 我饭后小睡呢
Go away! I'm on my lunch break.
不好意思 警官 这是95号路的匝道吗
Excuse me, officer. Is this the on-ramp to 95?
伙计
Socks.
操蛋的
I'll be fucked.
这是我搭档 Jimmy McNulty
This is my partner, Jimmy McNulty.
你看着像个要买新房的人
You look like a man in the market for a new house.
考虑考虑吧 现在是买家市场
Think about it. It's a buyer's market.
不错的花园
Nice garden.
你眼光不错 伙计
You have an eye for quality, Socks.
要挪窝的话给我打电话
Call me if you decide to move.
- 你来这不是要叙旧吧 - 我希望是
- So this isn't a social call? - I wish it were.
有话说吧 我明天有得忙呢 得休息
Well, get on with it. I got a busy day tomorrow, I need my rest.
Oscar 我们要一具尸体
Oscar, we're in need of a body -
男性 流浪汉 还没有或稍有点腐烂
male, homeless, little or no decomp.
没人注意的尸体?
Unattended death?
那没问题啊 你们不就在凶杀科吗
That shouldn't be no problem, seeing as you homicide.
我们得先人一步到场
We need to get to it before anybody else sees.
你们想造出个杀人案?
You want to open an H-file?
那得最早到场
Well, that's got to be a first.
我怎么联系你
How do I reach you?
好吧
All right.
想知道为什么吗
You want to know why?
就这样?
Is that it?
- 如果他帮我们... - McQuayle在凶杀科待过
- If he backs up on us... - McQuayle was in homicide.
他遇上一次拙劣的绑架
He caught one - a botched kidnapping.
他赶到那 发现地区主管在那闲荡
He gets there, finds the area chief sightseeing his scene,
让他一边去 他引用了行动指南
asks him to back off, cites the G.O.
G3 "协调调查的权责
G-3, "Authority and responsibility to coordinate the investigation
"在于凶杀警探"
"shall rest with the homicide detective."
地区主管很生气
Area chief takes umbrage.
Oscar坚持自己的立场 两人大吵了一架
Oscar stands his ground, and there's quite a dust-up.
第二天 他就被说成不服从上级命令
The next morning, he's told he's insubordinate.
他得在纪念馆大街额外巡逻两周
He's got to work two weeks extra duty pounding pavement.??
他跟他们说去他们的
He told them to go fuck themselves,
他要上裁定委员会
he'll take the trial board.
结果他还是接受了两周的惩罚
Well, he eats two weeks,
他们还把他踢出了小队
and they shitcan him out the unit.
地区主管?
Area chief?
记得叫Rawls
Name of Rawls, as I remember it.
你怎么还活着
How you still alive, yo?
他们要捎个口信 告诉他
They needed to send a message. Tell him.
他们说 "告诉Omar 他抢错人了"
Said, "Tell Omar he put his hand in the wrong pocket."
要知道 Marlo的伙计没让Butchie好过
You need to know, Marlo dogs, they didn't let Butchie go easy.
我要弄死他们 对天发誓 我要弄死他们
I'm gonna work them. Sweet Jesus, I'm gonna work them.
- 算我一个 - 不 这是我的事
- I want in. - Nah, this one on me, yo.
但你不认识他们
But you don't know them people.
不出所料 是Rawls  Daniels暂居副手
As expected, it's Rawls, with Daniels waiting in the wings.
难道他们不知道我当自己也是候选人吗
Did they not know that I made myself a candidate?
- 有种被玩弄的感觉 - Rawls终于混出头了
- I feel dissed. - So Rawls finally has his day.
也风光不久
Not much more than a day it shall be.
- 过完今年就是Daniels了 - 看这个
- Daniels by year's end. - Look at this.
- 你都不准备读读看吗 - 你不过是改个日期
- You're not even gonna read it? - All you do is change the date.
- 我在给自己擦屁股 Jay - 那你擦干净了
- I'm covering my ass, Jay. - Consider it covered.
混蛋 我是22具一年多的尸体的主要调查人
Motherfucker, I am the primary on 22 bodies more than a year old,
其中14个犯罪现场的分析报告还没给我
and I still haven't got trace analysis on 14 scenes.
实验室没空处理陈年旧案
The lab can't keep up with this year's cases.
你要行动 就让我看到些进展
You want action, show me some traction.
或者给自己买套化学仪器
Or buy yourself a chemistry set.
还在给我的受害者们做些背景调查 找些共通点
Just doing background on my vics, looking for a common thread.
混球 别...
Motherfucker, don't even...
去你的 混球
Fuck you, too, motherfucker.
Bunk怎么了
What's wrong with Bunk?
难说 那粗鲁的外表下 可是一颗玻璃心
Hard to say. Beneath that gruff veneer, he's actually very emotional.
再给你的流浪汉案子找主题是吧
Looking for the theme in  your homeless case,are you?
祝我好运吧
Well, wish me luck.
我得去询问我唯一的证人
I'm gonna try for an interview with my only wit.
那桩入室案?
The home invasion?
去他的 Tony 那家伙是个混球 你看他干的什么
Fuck him, Tony, the guy was an asshole.
你知道你昨天打的是谁吗 你他妈知道吗
You know who you were beating on yesterday? You fucking know?
老师 Stuart Hill小学的
A teacher, from Stuart Hill Elementary,
想绕过我们的破车去做课后辅导
trying to get around our bullshit to an after-school program.
- 他得跟我们说啊 - 他没机会开口
- He should have said so. - He never got a chance.
伙计 我也见过不少挫事
Boy, I seen some stupid shit in my day,
但就算以西区的标准来看 这也算标新立异了
but even by western standards, this rates a whole new category.
内部调查科正在跟局长谈话
I. I.D. Is talking to the major.
10分钟后就会来录口供
They're gonna be looking for statements in 10 minutes.
Tony 你得写得机灵点
Tony, you got to write this smart.
过分刺耳的喇叭让你在抓少年犯时分心...
The excessive horn blowing distracted you from securing juvenile prisoners who...
噪声让你有些失控
became volatile due to the noise,
你数次警告司机...
and you warned the driver several times...
去他的吧
Fuck that motherfucker.
- 什么 - 我说 去他的
- Say what? - I said, fuck him.
傻逼狂按喇叭 就该抓起来 去他妈的白痴
Shitbird lays on his horn. Fuck his ignorant ass.
监管警督请到警长办公室
Admin lieutenant to the major's office.
Tony 我要把你交出来
Tony, I'm writing you up.
暴力执法 行为失当
Excessive force, conduct unbecoming.
- 你不挺我? - 我要把责任推在你身上
- You ain't gonna back me? - I'm charging you.
你归咎于我 你就是告密者
You charge me, you're a fucking rat.
那我就是告密者好了
Then I'm a rat.
不 没门 我做了那么多事要把他扔下飞机
No. After what I've been through to toss him out of the plane,
你现在却让我给他备好降落伞?
now you want me to pretty  up his parachute?
局长为这个城市服务了34年
The commissioner served this city for 34 years.
五年就足够让他被告了
Any five of which would be enough to have him indicted.
你在逼着我 为你背后的开发商掠走...
You should have thought about this before you put a gun to my head
Mcculloh Homes时就该想到了
and snatched up the Mcculloh Homes for whatever developer you're hiding.
这不是为了我 也不是为了Burrell
This isn't about me, and it isn't even about Burrell.
是为了Daniels或任何 你想让其掌控警局的人
It's about Daniels or whoever else you want in that department.
- 为什么 - 34年是很长一段时间
- How so? - 34 years is a long time.
谁在位那么长时间 手上都握着不少小辫子 如果他说出去...
Anyone around that long can put his hands on a lot of dirt. If they talk...
- Daniels? - 我不是要特指谁
- Daniels? - I'm not being specific here.
我只是想表明 为了大家着想
I'm just making it clear  for everyone's sake
最好让Burrell安静地离开
it would be better if Burrell went quietly.
我们在中午安排了一个新闻发布会
We've scheduled a press conference for this afternoon.
我想Ervin准备好面对公众了
I think Ervin is ready for a little grip and grin.
跟你 跟Rawls...
With you, with Rawls...
为了相互体谅 他也许甚至愿意拥抱Daniels
For considerations, he might even put his arm around Daniels.
一个捐赠人给西区联合会的
Money from a donor to West Side Hoops.
存款日期
Deposit date.
从那个账户取出存入他的私人账户
Withdrawal from that account to his personal account.
又一笔捐赠人的钱
Again... money from a donor.
谢谢你能来 参议员
Thank you for coming, senator.
我们要求你来回答一些问题
We've asked you in to answer questions
事关某些财政上的不正常情况
regarding certain financial  irregularities.
我们可以先到我办公室聊聊或直接开始
We can go to my office and talk first or get right to it.
带路吧
Lead on.
那请跟我来
If you'll follow me, then.
他很冷静
He's pretty cool about it.
出来见分晓
The coming out tells the tale.
Devon?
你听过这个故事吗
Do you know this story?
要不要我念给你听
Or would you like me to read it to you?
Devon?
我向你展示的是一张 2007年1月22日的作废支票
Now, then, I show you a canceled check dated 22 January, 2007,
来自Sterner Ernst和Bauer发展集团
from Sterner, Ernst, and Bauer Development Group
付给西巴尔的摩联合会 总额1万1千
made payable to West Baltimore Hoops Incorporated in the amount of $11,000.
而这是2007年1月23日的...
And this dated 23 January, 2007,
西巴尔的摩联合会开出一张支票
a check drawn on the West Baltimore Hoops Incorporated account
总额1万1千
in the amount of $11,000.
同年1月23日 你的个人账户
And a deposit slip dated 23 January, same year,
增加了一笔总额1万1千的存款
to your personal account in the amount of $11,000.
我是来协助调查的 你们却含血喷人
I come here to help, but y'all out for blood.
我不会再回答任何问题了
I'm not answering no more questions.
你是援引无需自证其罪的权利吗 先生
You are invoking your right against self-incrimination, sir?
- 没错 - 那我们可以为这次作证下定论了
- Damn right. - Then we'll conclude this testimony.
靠
Damn.
这只是轻拍一下
And that was just a love tap.
想象一下我们把参议员 整个破事搬出来会怎样
Imagine if we hit the good senator with the whole shebang.
这么快就第五修正案了?
Quick on the fifth, huh?
那还要大陪审团做什么
Why did we even grand jury, then?
探员们 答案就在Calvert街上
The answer to that, detective, is out on Calvert Street.
参议员 我们想跟你谈谈
Senator, we'd like to talk to you.
参议员 请回答
Senator, please, over here.
参议员 你愿意发表一份声明吗
Senator, would you care to make a statement?
- 参议员 请回答 参议员 - 这儿 参议员
- Senator, please, senator! - Over here, senator.
你到庭是接受大陪审团询问的吗
Did you appear before the grand jury?
Jane 我是被传唤
Jane, I insisted that I be called.
参议员 就我们理解 你是盗窃和榨取案件的调查目标
Senator, aren't you the target of an investigation into theft and fraud?
不 什么 不 有些人对某些事有些混淆
No, pardon, no. Some people are confused about some things.
所以我今天才来这 把事情说清楚
But that's why I came here, to set them straight.
我也很乐意这么做 我很乐意为...
Happy to do it, too. Happy to avail myself of the...
大陪审团该秘密行事的 谁叫来的记者
Grand jury's supposed to be secret. Who called the reporters?
Bond先生 州律师...
Mr. Bond, our state's attorney...
在其他人之前就觊觎参议员的位置
Laying claim to the senator before anybody else can.
不过是对我在社区的交往情况
There just seemed to be a little bit of a misunderstanding
有点小误会
about my dealings here in the community.
等报纸不再盯着我
Yo, as soon as this newspaper stink get off my ass,
我就彻底不玩过家家 直接开战
I'm-a unload my club and clear a mil.
我要染指每一块我未染指的区域
I'm gonna snatch up every vacant I can get my fingers on.
这才对 像个真正的玩家
There you go. Like a real player.
这是个新的世界了 伙计 买些房产
It's a whole new world, man. Buy some property.
攥着等白人来了 狠狠宰上一笔
Hold onto it till white people show up, you make a killing.
Milton就玩这套 只不过 他跟那什么鬼囚犯重回社会计划合作
Milton's into that, except he got a deal with that bullshit prisoner entry program.
- 让囚犯替他修房子 - 混球们...
- Got convicts fixing up his house. - Motherfuckers...
闭嘴
shut the fuck up.
你们的破事听得我恶心
I'm sick of listening to your shit.
我们有生意吗 如果没有 我们得找点生意
Have we got business? If we ain't, we gonna bounce.
Marlo看样子赶时间
Marlo here seems pressed for time.
你们可以会后再谈
So y'all can pick back up on this after the meeting.
下面要说话的是Hungry Man
Last up. We got Hungry Man.
你侄子自把自为地
Junior here took it upon himself to make unlawful incursions
入侵了县里我的人的地盘
into county territory marked for my people.
入侵? 那里可不算是你的地盘 贱人
Incursions?Ain't you the articulate motherfucker?
你再说 我赏你一耳光
Keep talking, you gonna get spanked.
你敢吗 撒尿都跟个娘们似的
Like you got the heart. Motherfucker piss like a bitch.
好了 够了
All right, shut it down.
就我所知 你原本还无权列席的
Last I look, you wasn't no charter member.
抱歉
I apologize.
我侄子会注意地盘界限的 我保证
My nephew gonna heed the boundaries, I assure you.
好了 休会
A'ight, meeting's adjourned.
这儿怎么回事
What the fuck up in here?
- 跟我说的一样 对吧 - 嗯
- Just like I told you, right? - Yeah.
我取了点出来带回家
I pulled some of it out, brought it back home.
我...
I was...
我在想...
I was thinking...
接下来拿这个怎么办
what next with this?
你明天抽出点时间
You clear some time tomorrow,
我等着你大驾光临 行吗
I'll open the door for you. That work?
孩子...
Son...
你该多关注合作的好处
you need to focus a bit more on what can be gained by working with people.
那现在还只是个想法
That's just a thought, now.
嗯
Yeah.
谢了
Thanks.
来看一具行尸走肉吗
Come to see a dead man walking?
听说Carcetti会善待你
I hear Carcetti's gonna do right by you.
领协调委员会的薪水 接着去特区工作
Salary with the coordinating council, then a D.C. Job.
- 你应得的 - 是啊 我应得的
- You deserve it. - Sure, I deserve it,
但不是因为我的工作
but not for doing the job.
我所有的 都是这么些年来他们让我做的
What I got, they gave me for carrying their water all these years.
在Carcetti眼里 我是个雇佣文人
To Carcetti, I'm a hack.
Royce也没区别
Royce was no different.
也许我就是 但他们朝令夕改
Maybe I am. But every day they send over a new priority.
抓坏蛋 不 变一下
Go after the bad guys. No, change that.
办生活质量的案子 优先调查谋杀案
Make quality-of-life cases. Get on top of the murders.
转念一想 又要把妓女赶出Patterson公园
On second thought, run the whores out of Patterson Park.
你以为市长告诉学校怎么教学生
You think the mayor tells the schools how to teach kids,
教健康部门干活 或教公共卫生部怎么捡垃圾?
or the health department how to do its job, or sanitation how to pick up trash?
一旦当选 他们就突然间知道怎么干警察了
But get elected, and suddenly, they know police work.
你可能以为会有所不同...
You might think it'll be different...
等你坐在这...
when you sit here...
一切还是一样
but it won't.
你只能干他们交代的破事
You will eat their shit.
Daniels坐上这位置也一样
Daniels, too, when he gets here.
我想知道你怎么找到梯子上去
I wonder how you get the ladder to go up.
怎么办
How do you do that?
这是个很好的救火车
This is a wonderful fire truck.
消防员上哪去了呢
I wonder where all the firemen are.
你觉得他们能坐得进来吗
Think they could fit in here?
这个汽笛会发出什么声音
I wonder what kind of siren sound this makes.
Cheryl 嗨
Cheryl, hey.
我想过去看看Elijah
I was thinking I might want to swing by and see Elijah, you know?
我知道有一阵子了 但...
Yeah, I know it's been a while. But...
不 我可以安排的
No, I can get off.
明天可以
Yeah, tomorrow'd be fine.
嗯 好的
Yeah. Sure.
我就回来
I'll be right back.
- 抱歉 我不认为... - 没关系
- I'm sorry. I just don't think... - No, it's OK.
现在他太自闭了 很难回忆事发当时的情况
Right now, he's too withdrawn to revisit the event.
谁愿意想起那种事
How do you come back from something like that?
你看上去很紧张 副局长
You look nervous, Deputy.
我发誓不是我要求的
I swear I didn't ask for this.
放松
Relax.
你曾告诉我 如果我对付你 你就玩完了 记得吗
You once told me that if I was gonna do you, you'd be done already. Remember?
靠 我不记得文件里是什么了
Shit, I don't even remember what was in that file.
东区分局的什么事吧
Something about the eastern district.
那么久远
So long ago,
谁记得住
who can remember?
我想说一些关于公共服务
I wanted to say a few words about public service
和Ervin H. Burrell的事
and about Ervin H. Burrell.
我在市议会工作时 Erv与我相熟
During my time on the city council, Erv was no stranger to me.
我主持公众安全委员会时见过他几次
I chaired the public safety subcommittee, and I called upon him many times.
我们合作无间 我当上市长后 我们建立了牢固的关系...
We worked closely and when I became mayor, we formed a strong relationship...
他害怕并讨厌我 而我只是欲除之而后快
He feared and hated me, and I merely wanted him dead.
...让巴尔的摩变成一个安全的城市
...making Baltimore a safer city.
别在内港游荡
Don't stray from the inner harbor.
但是我知道 刑事司法协调理事会需要新的领导...
The criminal justice coordinating council needs new leadership...
花了点时间 但我终于让他滚蛋了
It took a while, but I finally put his ass out to pasture.
请 谢谢
If you would. Thank you.
雇佣文人的牌匾
Plaques for hacks.
大城市市长的特权
Prerogative of any big-city mayor.
在明天的报纸上要体现多少 这种深刻的洞察力
How much of that insight and analysis can we get in tomorrow's story?
一点点都不行
Little to none.
Twigg会继续跟进局里的消息来源
Twigg could work the department sources,
他们会继续演这狗血的戏码
and they would shit all over a dog-and-pony show like that.
市政厅里的Price呢
What about Price at the hall?
市长办公室召开的新闻发布会
Mayor's office set up the press conference.
他们不会说实话 甚至连背景都不说
They're not gonna tell the truth. Not even the background.
一个警队里的老兵给了我们 这么个故事助我们渡过难关
No, a veteran in the cop shop gets us over on a story like this,
我们不大卖才怪
and fuck if we didn't buy ours out.
Gus 我知道你不满裁员
Gus, I understand that you're disappointed with the cutbacks,
但礼貌很重要
but civility is important.
我一直想跟你说说你的脏话
I've been meaning to talk to you about your profanity.
我的脏话?
My profanity?
学院氛围至关重要
A collegial atmosphere is essential.
学院? 我他妈新闻系都读不过来
Collegial? I fucking failed out of journalism school.
- 他妈的"学院"什么玩意 - 老天 我们没报道这个?
- What the fuck do "collegial" mean? - Christ, we don't have this?
检察人员对一次 疑似大陪审团会议未发表评论
Prosecutors would not comment on a possible grand jury investigation,
但知情人士称参议员已经被调查了
but sources familiar with the case say the senator has been under investigation
- 一年之久 - Zorzi!
- for more than a year. - Zorzi!
助理州检察官Rhonda Pearlman...
Assistant state's attorney Rhonda Pearlman...
Clay Davis今天被大陪审团传讯
Clay Davis was grand-juried today.
他已经被查腐败案一年了
He's been under investigation for a year.
我是个联邦法庭记者 记得吗
I'm a federal court reporter, remember?
自从Doug Strock被买断后 我们就没有日常跟进市法庭的人了
We haven't had daily city court coverage since Doug Strock took the buyout before last.
- 这不是联邦的调查? - 那我早知道了 这是市里做的
- This isn't a federal probe? - I would have had that. This is city.
你想让一个记者跟进两个法庭 可以
You want one reporter covering two courthouses, fine.
干嘛不在我屁股上塞个扫帚 我还能边走边扫地呢
Why not shove the broom up my ass, and I'll sweep the floor while I'm at it.
好吧 跟上后续的报道 行吧
All right. Just get caught up, OK?
看看能不能让Davis说点什么
See if you can get a quote from Davis.
Scott 跟着Zorzi报道法庭的事
Scott, chase a courthouse story with Zorzi.
- 没问题 有什么要求 - 找州检察官
- What do you need? - Find the state's attorney.
他今天在大陪审团庭外阴了Clay Davis
He set up Clay Davis outside the grand jury today.
找Bond 他会让我们跟上这个事
Get hold of Bond, he'll catch us up on this shit.
老天
Jesus.
还记得不给日报打电话就不起诉的
Remember the good old days when nobody would stage a perp walk
旧日好时光吗
without calling a daily newspaper?
现在 他们只在乎电视
Nowadays, all they care about is a goddamn video.
- 他们忘了 - 我不知道我们为什么要这么做
- They've forgotten. - I don't know why we're doing this.
这种报告我睡着了都写得出来
I can write a report like this in my sleep.
Jay绝不会检查我的所作所为
There's no way Jay checks what I'm doing.
Jimmy 很多事情都指望这个了
Jimmy, a lot rides on this.
像个真正的案子一样办 那它就会像个真正的案子
Work it like a real case, it'll feel like a real case,
更重要的是 读起来也会像个真正的案子
and more importantly, it'll read like a real case.
你该看看我今天在小组办公室里的样子
I was in the squad room today,
摆得像我迷失在生涯最重要的一次调查中
all the case work laid out like I'm lost in a career case.
- Landsman却几乎视而不见 - 我们做好准备
- Landsman barely noticed. - We crank this up,
不会只有Landsman看这份谋杀卷宗
Landsman's not the only one who's gonna be thumbing through this H-file.
稍有疏失 我们就会锒铛入狱
We get sloppy, we get cuffed.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
做警探该做的事 警探
What detectives do, detective.
能聊聊吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
待会儿吧 我得做好干活的准备
Maybe later. I got to get ready for work.
- 你的狗咬人吗 - 他有牙 不是吗
- Does your dog bite? - Got teeth, don't he?
Chip Change 来这儿坐 好样的
Chip change, get your ass in here. That's it.
我是McNulty警探 凶杀科的
I'm Detective McNulty, Homicide.
能问你些问题吗
Can I ask you a few questions?
你有卡吗
Oh Got a card?
You got a card?
- 卡 - 名片
- Card? - Business card, yeah.
这个... 这才是卡
This... That is a card.
不!
No!
好玩吗
We having fun yet?
我要喝酒
I need a drink.
我只问你一遍 Joe在哪
I'm gonna ask you once, where Joe?
别说了
Skip past the talking.
爱咋咋地
Do what you feel.
Joe跟这事无关...
Joe ain't had nothing to do with...
Slim 你可不想我弄疼你
Now, Slim, you gonna make me hurt you, yo.
伙计 你自己想想 Joe为什么要把Butchie供出来
Ask yourself, dog,  why would Joe give Butchie up?
如果Marlo能让他招了
If Marlo could make him talk,
那Joe也脱不了干系
he puts Joe inside your big score.
如果你觉得Joe会供出Butchie 我就告诉你
If Joe turned Butchie, I'd tell you.
靠 我甚至可以帮你
Shit, I help you, even.
但完全不是那么回事
But it just ain't like that.
来吧
Come on, yo.
做个了断吧
Finish it.
看看第五张图
Take a look at the fifth graph.
"市长 逗号 被局长的表现激怒..."
"The mayor, comma, incensed by the commissioner's performance..."
- "激怒"似乎有点过分啊 - 不知道
- "Incensed" seems over the top. - I don't know.
毒品合法化的惨败 空屋藏尸
Drug legalization fiasco, the bodies in the vacants,
狗屁的统计数据 换我也会怒
the bullshit stats. I'd be incensed.
Jay 看看Arnold的第五张图
Hey Jay, take a look at Arnold's fifth graph.
好
OK.
"激怒"是怒火爆发
"Incensed" is to inflame with wrath.
说太狠了 这是市长内心的想法吗
It speaks to obsession. Is this the mayor's state of mind?
也许该用更微妙些的词
Something more nuanced, perhaps.
着恼 生气 恼怒...
Galled, vexed, annoyed...
更保险的... 不满
Safer still... displeased.
你这是把螃蟹从螃蟹汤里捞出来了
You'd take the crab out of crab soup.
Scott 你和Zorzi干得不错 我们跟上进度了
Hey, Scott, that was good work by you and Zorzi catching us up.
- 干得好 - 这是夸你呢
- Great effort. - There's an "attaboy" for you.
华盛顿那边怎么样了
How'd it go in Washington?
买家市场啊
Buyer's market out there.
都市新闻部开会
Metro desk.
巴尔的摩太阳报也不坏
Baltimore Sun ain't so bad.
9A43
9-Adam-4-3.
接警 生死不明 老Compton大楼后巷
Reported D.O.A., alley in the rear of the old Compton plant.
收到 生死不明
Copy D.O.A.
9A46 KGA
9-46. K-G-A,
告诉43 我在附近 可以处理
Advise 43 I'm close by. I'll handle it.
收到 9A46
Copy, 9-Adam-46.
Bunk 你还好吧 她说的是"生死不明" 不是"甜甜圈"
Bunk, are you feeling all right? She said "D.O.A.," not "doughnut."
我知道你们行动低调
I know y'all into keeping things on the hush-hush tip,
但该死的 这档子CIA行事风格很牛逼
but, damn, Chris, this C. I.A. Shit off the hook.
我...
I...
我最近没做什么惹毛你们的事吧
I ain't done nothing lately to piss you off, right?
对吧
Right?
他已经吓得失禁了
Man already shit hisself,
我们还没开始呢
and we ain't even get started yet.
臭死了
He's funky, yo.
Marlo给你的礼物 你知道该怎么办
It's a gift from Marlo. But you know how that go.
礼尚往来
Give a gift, get a gift.
Hungry Man 你好吗
Yo, Hungry Man, what's up?
- 喂 - Lester 你可以回去了
- Hello? - Lester, you can turn around.
- 不理想? - 嗯 假警报
- Bad call? - Yeah, false alarm.
好吧
All right.
没用 死太久了
Won't work. He's too far gone.
我找人 警探 你要做什么是你的事
I find them, detective. What you do after that is your business.
谢了 下次吧
Thanks. Maybe next time.
看在我热心帮忙的份上 警探
Seeing as how I'm doing you a favor, detective,
你可以替我写首个到达现场警员的报告
you can write the first officer's report for me.
我的序列号是A115
My sequence is A-1-15.
我认识他 Avon的律师
I know him. Avon's lawyer.
也是我的律师 Brick也用他
Yeah, mine, too. Brick uses him.
还有Phil Boy的生意多让他处理 不光是犯罪
So does Phil Boy for most of his stuff, not just the criminal side.
Levy很擅长让我们的黑钱发挥作用
Yeah, Levy excels in putting our limp-dick money to work.
你想知道怎么处理那些银行支票?
You want to know what to do with them bank checks?
就上这儿来
This where you need to be.
Joseph 你看着很旺嘛
Joseph, you're looking prosperous.
得过且过吧
I get by.
Stanfield先生
Mr. Stanfield.
Joseph跟我说过你不少好话
Joseph tells me good things about you.
你摄像头找到了吗
You ever find that camera?
把我工作都赔上了
Cost me the job.
我们进会议室详谈吧
So let's go into the conference room where we can spread out.
这是你和你律师间的事
This between you and your attorney.
Carcetti终于踢掉了Burrell
Carcetti finally dumps Burrell.
Ervin是在Dunbar高中高我一届的学长
Ervin was a year before me at Dunbar.
不是吧
No shit.
他还参加过合唱团
He was in the glee club.
我忍不住了 一定要问
You're killing me. I got to ask.
蠢得可以
Stone stupid.
Elijah? 跟Kima阿姨打个招呼
Elijah? Say hi to Aunt Kima.
总之 你来得正是时候
Anyways, you were right on time with this.
我还有很多事要做
I got a dozen things to get done,
只能在台里加班加点
and I got to do them while working overtime at the station.
- 忙个不停? - 是啊 老板被炒了
- Been busy, huh? - Yeah. Your boss got fired,
那之后我们就不停东奔西走
and we've been running ever since.
再见 Lij
Bye, Lij.
去吧 我们没问题的
Go on. We'll be fine.
哇哦 真不错
Wow, that's good.
都涂在线里面呢
You staying inside the lines.
想做点什么吗
Hey, you want to do something?
去公园?
Go to the park?
吃冰激凌?
Get some ice cream?
你说什么
What did you say?
你没有房子
You don't have a house?
那算什么事啊 英雄需要房子
What's up with that? A hero needs a house.
我上次盖好房子已经是很久前的事了
Been a long time since I built a house.
希望我还记得
Hope I remember how.
副局长办公室
Deputy ops.
不 我是Daniels Cedric Daniels
No, this is Daniels. Cedric Daniels.
他在局长办公室
He's now in the commissioner's office.
是的
Yes.
他知道他搞砸了 他知道
He knows he fucked up. He knows this.
他很骄傲 不想求你
He's proud, you know? He doesn't want to beg.
我不是为了这个
It's not about that.
拜托 Carv
Come on, Carv.
你不能搞自己人
You cannot do one of your own guys.
我是说 我知道你现在升了 你都快做警督了 但还是...
I mean, I know you got rank now, you're damn near lieutenant, but still...
跟警衔无关
It ain't about the rank.
我从没跟你说过 Herc
I never told you, Herc.
从没说过
Never said a fucking word.
记得我去年带个孩子去找你汇报情况吗
But when I gave you that kid to debrief last year?
你本该带他去找Bunk Moreland 记得吗
You were supposed to get him to Bunk Moreland. Remember?
嗯 我搞砸了 那又怎么样
Yeah. I fucked up. So what?
那很重要
So it mattered.
这跟Colicchio有什么关系
What the fuck does this have to do with Colicchio?
关系大了 我知道我们觉得没关系...
It all matters. I know we thought it didn't, but...
但有关系
it does.
所以你要搞Colicchio?
So you got to do Colicchio, huh?
我想你也觉得他们一定会整我吧
Guess you think they had to do me.
大概吧
Yeah, probably.
这些家伙会说一段时间你的坏话
These guys are gonna talk shit about you for a while.
但去他们的 Carv 你该怎么做就怎么做
But fuck 'em, Carv. You do what needs done.
- 我一点出去的  - 你八点到四点当班
- I was out on one.  - You worked 8 to 4.
我在查一个连环杀手 一有可疑的死亡他们就会找我
I'm working a serial killer. They call me on any suspicious death.
是吗 他们在哪联系上你的
Yeah? Where'd they reach you?
我不骗你 我回家路上喝了一两杯 接着就接到了电话
Well, I'm not gonna lie. I... stopped, had a couple, then I got the call.
我知道 从这我都能闻到 你身上Jameson酒的味道
I know. I can smell the Jameson's from here.
还有Jamie和Listerine的味道
Jamie and Listerine, your scent.
Beadie... 我...
Beadie... I'm just...
我们出问题了 Jimmy 你和我 出问题了
We had something, Jimmy. You and me, we had something.
你知道 别人告诉我你的事 告诉我你过去是怎样的人
you know When people told me  stories about you, about how you were,
我不信 我无法想象
I couldn't believe it. I couldn't see it.
喂
Yeah.
好的 10分钟
Yeah. 10 minutes.
又有一具尸体 南巴尔的摩
I got another one. South Baltimore.
- Beadie 我在追查一个连环杀手 - 你追的不只是一个杀手
- Beadie, I'm chasing a serial killer. - That's not all you're chasing.
听着 如果你不想住在这...
Look, if you don't want to be here...
我得走了
I got to go.
他换地方了
He changed up.
Marlo不傻 他知道你会报复的
Marlo's no fool.  He know you be coming at him.
江湖传言 他和Chris开战了
Word is, him and Chris went to the mattresses,
几乎每晚都挪地方
on the move almost every night.
- 他傻到会唤醒一只沉睡的狮子 - 那应该会给你些启示
- Fool enough to kick a sleeping dog. - That should tell you something.
他等着我 我不会直接找他
I got the boy waiting on me, I ain't go at him straight up.
我要对付他的人 懂吗 你除掉得够多
I go after his people, you feel me? You hurt enough of them,
那条蛇自然会从洞中探出头来
that snake gonna stick his head above that hole.
那边那个你认识吗
That one there, you know him?
他是个副手
He's a lieutenant.
我们先对他下手
We gonna go after him first.
记住那车
Yo Mark that ride, yo.
Oscar
Oscar.
- Lester - 谢了 小子
- Lester. - Thank you, baby.
- 随时效劳 伙计 - 嗯 好的
- Yeah Anytime, man. - Yeah. All right.
很完美 死了不到几个小时
He's perfect. Can't be dead more than a couple of hours.
最好把这些处理掉
Better lose these.
你真他妈变态 McNulty
You're a twisted fuck, McNulty.
自卫伤 这才有人信
Defense wounds. Help sell it.
你还敢说我变态 牙齿可是你提出来的
You got nerve calling me twisted. You came up with the teeth.
你知道这些连环杀人狂是咋回事
You know how these psycho serial motherfuckers are.
他们会成长的
They mature.
一开始简单粗暴
They start simple and crude
接着越来越华丽 给
and become more and more ornate.  There you go.
别告诉我妈或我的牧师 你看见我做这个
Don't tell my mother or my priest you saw me do this.
我会把秘密带进坟墓的
Take it to my grave.
- 要我拿吗 - 不 我来就行了
- Want me to take that? - Nah, I got it.
你在这洞里看见了什么 你的全部财产吗
What you see in this hole, man? All the money you got?
你曾祖父
Your great-grandfather,
第一个在Johnson广场 有自己屋子的有色人种
first colored man to own his own house in Johnson Square.
那意味着一些特质 一些你们年轻人失去的特质
That means something, Something you young'uns lost.
你准备好的话 我们在外面
Yeah. Well, we outside when you ready.
我走后留神点 Charles说Omar回来了
Hey Keep sharp while I'm gone, boy. Charles say Omar back.
他留了Charles一命 但碰上你和你手下
He left Charles standing  but he might feel less inclined
他可能就没那么心慈手软了
if he get the drop on you or yours.
我才不怕Omar
Ain't got to fret none about Omar.
不必了
No need for that.
你不是来送我的
You ain't come to see me off.
我侄子
My nephew.
这孩子老是让我失望
Boy was always a disappointment.
但我对你像对我孩子一样
But I treated you like a son.
我可不是来给你当儿子的
I wasn't made to play the son.
那我的货源 那些上乘毒品呢
But my supply - the good dope?
希腊人没意见了
The Greeks, they cool with it.
那我提议
Proposition, then -
我给你让路
I just step out the way.
你不会再听到我的消息 我会从此消失
You never hear from me again. I just disappear.
Joe 你很快又会兴风作浪的
Joe, you'd be up into mischief in no time.
事实上 你没我那么变化多端
Truth is, you wouldn't be able to change up any more than me.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
不会痛的
It won't hurt none.
来吧
There, now.
Joe 放松
Joe, relax.
轻轻呼吸
Breathe easy.